{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Waterproofing Inspectors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40449/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40449,"taskName":"Inspection - Waterproofing","taskDescription":"Waterproof Inspection / Certification Service","xmTaskDescriptor":"Waterproofing Inspectors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":269,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Inspection Waterproofing foundation inpsection","textMessagingName":"Insp Waterproof","rolloverLongDesc":"Many waterproofing companies offer free inspection as part of their sales effort. While often sources of valuable information, the analysis is not neutral \u0026 usually results in the recommendation of their company's solution. For truly neutral, more informed advice, hire an independent inspector to investigate options. Most independent inspectors are home inspectors who specialize wet basement problems.","rolloverShortDesc":"Analyze wet basement or certify dry basement problems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Waterproof Inspection / Certification Service.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Waterproof Inspection \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":83,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Waterproofing Inspection","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Inspection - Waterproofing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Waterproofing Inspection Need","urlName":"Inspection-Waterproofing","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Waterproof Inspection Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Inspection,Waterproofing,foundation,inpsection","emcCategoryOid":-12078,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":740,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40449/":{"taskOID":40449,"originalTaskOID":40449,"setID":740,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4656,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for inspection","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need a waterproof inspection service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and test an item","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and test an item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2260,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5393,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Roof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6917,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof awareness program","answerDisplayText":"Roof awareness program","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","answerDisplayText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":825,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Appraisal","answerDisplayText":"Appraisal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Retrofitting advice","answerDisplayText":"Retrofitting advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5405,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof management","answerDisplayText":"Roof management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5946,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Specification writing","answerDisplayText":"Specification writing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2299,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Expert witness in litigation","answerDisplayText":"Expert witness in litigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":720,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air seal inspection","answerDisplayText":"Air seal inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1806,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","answerDisplayText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4657,"questionDisplayText":"Inspection needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For testing and evaluation, what specific item in your home needs to be inspected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1579,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete or masonry patio","answerDisplayText":"Concrete or masonry patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3099,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"House siding","answerDisplayText":"House siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":726,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"All items","answerDisplayText":"All items","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4656,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for inspection","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need a waterproof inspection service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and test an item","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and test an item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2260,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5393,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Roof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6917,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof awareness program","answerDisplayText":"Roof awareness program","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","answerDisplayText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":825,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Appraisal","answerDisplayText":"Appraisal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Retrofitting advice","answerDisplayText":"Retrofitting advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5405,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof management","answerDisplayText":"Roof management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5946,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Specification writing","answerDisplayText":"Specification writing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2299,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Expert witness in litigation","answerDisplayText":"Expert witness in litigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":720,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air seal inspection","answerDisplayText":"Air seal inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1806,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","answerDisplayText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and test an item","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and test an item","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2260,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5393,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Roof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6917,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproof consultation","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof awareness program","answerDisplayText":"Roof awareness program","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","answerDisplayText":"Pre-purchase evaluation (new construction)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":825,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Appraisal","answerDisplayText":"Appraisal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5349,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Retrofitting advice","answerDisplayText":"Retrofitting advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5405,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof management","answerDisplayText":"Roof management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5946,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Specification writing","answerDisplayText":"Specification writing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2299,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Expert witness in litigation","answerDisplayText":"Expert witness in litigation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":720,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Air seal inspection","answerDisplayText":"Air seal inspection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1806,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","answerDisplayText":"Damage evaluation for insurance claims","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4657,"questionDisplayText":"Inspection needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For testing and evaluation, what specific item in your home needs to be inspected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1579,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete or masonry patio","answerDisplayText":"Concrete or masonry patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3099,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"House siding","answerDisplayText":"House siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":726,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"All items","answerDisplayText":"All items","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1579,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Concrete or masonry patio","answerDisplayText":"Concrete or masonry patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3099,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"House siding","answerDisplayText":"House siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":726,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"All items","answerDisplayText":"All items","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}